this problem
asks us to use an intel loop to print
each element of the numbers array to the
screen
and looking at the example output we can
see that we want to print
each number to the screen on its own
line
one simple way to access individual
elements of an array
is by using their index and we know that
arrays have a zero-based index
because arrays have a zero-based index
the index of the last element of the
array
will be one less than the size of the
let's initialize a local variable count
and set it equal to zero as we iterate
through the numbers array
we can use this variable to access
elements at
each index of the array initially
beginning at index 0
which is the first element of the array
[Music]
so let's create the skeleton of our
until loop
now we know we need to provide a
condition to this until loop
and when the condition evaluates to true
the loop will stop
iterating if we want to use the index
of each element of the array to access
these numbers
we can stop when the index is equal to
the size of the array
and again that's because the index of
the last element of the array
will always be one less than the size of
the array
within the loop we know that we need to
increment our variable count on each
iteration
so that we're moving through the array
and eventually
reaching the size of the array so that
our loop will stop executing and not
become infinite
and just to see this in action let's
output the count
and run our code
as you can see we increment count from
zero to four
and that will access each element of
this five element array
we've already done most of the heavy
lifting here
now all we need to do is use the count
variable
to access and output the appropriate
element of the array
and we can do that using the following
syntax
[Music]
we're now calling put s on the element
of the numbers array
at the given index which will be
anywhere from 0 to 4.
because we're calling put s which stands
for put string
each of these numbers will be printed on
their own line as a string
object
okay and we can see that our output
matches the expected output